【The fate that cannot be liberated】
[해방될 수 없는 운명]
[Episode 8]
[8화]
Do you understand what I'm saying?
내가 말하는 것을 이해 했어?
Bring the teapot. I want to drink.
찻주전자를 가져오세요. 나는 마시고 싶다.
I am He Jiuling.
나는 He Jiuling입니다.
At least you can understand my actions today.
적어도 당신은 오늘 내 행동을 이해할 수 있습니다.
Worth celebrating.
축하할 가치가 있습니다.
Put on your shoes. The ground is cold.
신발을 신으세요. 땅이 차갑습니다.
shoe.
구두.
Miss,
놓치다,
I've brought you what you want.
당신이 원하는 것을 가져왔습니다.
This is the sweet potato you want.
이것이 당신이 원하는 고구마입니다.
Your food is almost gone
음식이 거의 다 떨어졌어요
And you still give your best to strangers.
그리고 당신은 여전히 ​​낯선 사람들에게 최선을 다합니다 .
Everyone who comes is a guest.
오는 사람은 모두 손님이다.
Moreover, these two people are very pitiful.
게다가 이 두 사람은 참 불쌍하다.
We should treat them well.
우리는 그들을 잘 대해야 합니다.
You are so kind. I'm leaving now.
당신은 정말 친절해요. 나는 지금 떠난다.
careful.
주의 깊은.
here. Eat a sweet potato.
여기. 고구마를 먹어보세요.
Thank you ma'am.
감사합니다 사모님.
This is my husband.
이 사람은 내 남편이에요.
He's like your boyfriend. He didn't speak either.
그 사람 꼭 네 남자친구 같잖아 그도 말을 하지 않았습니다.
Your husband looks very strong
남편이 정말 강해 보여요
and have the ability to work.
그리고 일할 수 있는 능력이 있습니다.
He is different from my boyfriend
그 사람은 내 남자친구랑 달라요
People who are unable to speak and are physically weak.
말을 할 수 없고 신체적으로 허약한 사람.
But he's nice to you.
하지만 그 사람은 당신에게 친절해요.
Eat it yourself.
직접 먹어보세요.
I know how to use a spoon.
나는 숟가락 사용법을 안다.
I have never seen a couple as devoted as you two.
나는 당신들만큼 헌신적인 커플을 본 적이 없습니다.
Maybe your father doesn't have enough insight into men.
어쩌면 당신의 아버지는 남자에 대한 통찰력이 충분하지 않을 수도 있습니다.
It doesn't matter whether a person is strong or not.
사람이 강한지 아닌지는 중요하지 않습니다.
The important thing is that he is good to the people he loves.
중요한 것은 그가 사랑하는 사람들에게 좋은 사람이라는 것입니다.
There is such a young master
그런 젊은 주인이 있어요
Lowering my dignity to take care of you
너를 보살피기 위해 내 품위를 낮추고
You are lucky.
너는 운이 좋아.
If that's not enough for your father to let you marry him
당신의 아버지가 당신과 결혼하는 것을 허락하는 것만으로는 충분하지 않다면
He must be blind.
그 사람은 시각 장애인임에 틀림없어요.
Let me give you a suggestion.
제안을 하나 드리겠습니다.
Stay at my house for a few more days
며칠만 더 우리 집에 있어줘
Don't go back until you two have had your baby.
두 사람이 아기를 낳을 때까지 돌아가지 마세요.
unnecessary.
불필요한.
We'll leave tomorrow.
우리는 내일 떠날 것이다.
We are going to visit a relative.
우리는 친척을 방문할 예정이다.
Is this relatively reliable?
이게 상대적으로 믿을만 한가요?
Don't worry.
괜찮아요.
That relative will definitely take us in.
그 친척이 분명 우리를 데려갈 거예요.
Can't you just keep feeding me?
나한테 계속 먹이를 줄 수는 없나요?
give me a break,
나에게 휴식을 줘,
You can?
당신은 할 수 있습니까?
Eat it yourself.
직접 먹어보세요.
I can eat it myself. look.
내가 직접 먹을 수 있어요. 바라보다.
When you eat by yourself, you are normal.
혼자 먹으면 평범해요.
But you feed me like a pig.
그런데 당신은 나를 돼지처럼 먹여요.
Madam, this is our gift to thank you for letting us stay.
부인, 저희를 머물게 해주셔서 감사하다는 선물 입니다 .
No, I can't accept that.
아니요, 저는 그것을 받아들일 수 없습니다.
I'm just letting you stay for one night.
하룻밤만 묵게 해줄게요.
I didn't do anything else.
나는 다른 일을 하지 않았습니다.
I can't accept that much money.
나는 그 많은 돈을 받아들일 수 없다.
Take it.
가져.
Please buy me some casual clothes.
평상복 좀 사주세요.
I'll finish it after the meal.
식사 후에 끝내겠습니다.
Take care of each other on the road and live well.
길에서 서로 배려하며 잘 살아요.
Thank you ma'am.
감사합니다 사모님.
Then we left.
그런 다음 우리는 떠났습니다.
careful.
주의 깊은.
Be good. Don't run around.
잘 지내세요. 뛰어다니지 마세요.
Master Rong?
롱 선생님?
Master Rong!
룽 선생님!
Master!
주인!
Miss He?
미스 그?
Why are you dressed like this?
왜 이런 옷을 입고 있나요?
you? ? ?
너? ? ?
You must have mistaken me for someone else.
저를 다른 사람으로 착각하신 게 틀림없어요.
Please do not follow us. I am afraid.
우리를 따르지 마십시오. 나는 두렵다.
Are you scared?
너 두렵 니?
You kicked me too hard just now
너 지금 나를 너무 세게 걷어찼어
You still said you were afraid?
아직도 두렵다고 했나요?
You've exposed yourself, okay?
당신은 자신을 노출시켰어요, 그렇죠?
Miss He, so
Miss He, 그래서
The person next to you must be Master Rong.
당신 옆에 있는 사람은 Master Rong임에 틀림없습니다.
no doubt.
의심의 여지가 없습니다.
I've been drawing pictures of him for many years. I can't be wrong.
나는 수년 동안 그의 그림을 그려왔습니다 . 나는 틀릴 수 없습니다.
Oh, heaven.
아, 천국.
Master Rong finally woke up!
롱 사부가 마침내 일어났습니다!
Master Rong, Master Rong.
룽 선생님, 룽 선생님.
Is he really a fool now?
이제 그 사람 정말 바보인가?
My livelihood!
나의 생계!
I can't sell books.
나는 책을 팔 수 없어요.
I feel bad.
기분이 나빠요.
He will always be the master of star selection.
그는 언제나 스타 선택의 달인이 될 것이다.
When I take him to Wuhua Mountain, everything will be fine.
내가 그를 Wuhua Mountain으로 데려가면 모든 것이 잘 될 것입니다.
Then let's go.
그럼 가자.
Why are you crawling around here?
왜 여기를 기어다니는 걸까요?
Didn't you notice they were searching everywhere?
그들이 여기저기 수색하고 있다는 걸 모르셨나요 ?
Looking for you?
당신을 찾고 계십니까?
He is the young master of Xingxiang Pavilion
그는 Xingxiang Pavilion의 젊은 주인입니다.
and His Majesty's favorite minister.
그리고 폐하께서 가장 좋아하시는 장관이십니다.
I guess the capital is probably in chaos now.
아마 지금 수도가 혼란에 빠진 것 같아요.
Even this small city has checkpoints.
이 작은 도시에도 검문소가 있습니다.
But, but, aren't you already married?
그런데, 그런데, 이미 결혼하지 않으셨나요?
No one believes you can save him.
아무도 당신이 그를 구할 수 있다고 믿지 않습니다.
he and I? ? ?
그와 나? ? ?
forget it.
잊어 버려.
Just follow him for now.
지금은 그를 따라가세요.
I'm going to the post office to see if there's any hitchhikers.
히치하이커가 있는지 알아보려고 우체국에 갈 거예요 .
Your hand is hurt. I'll ask.
손이 다쳤어요. 내가 물어 볼게요.
that's it.
그게 다야.
Then asked them if there was a carriage to Shidu.
그런 다음 Shidu까지 마차가 있는지 물었습니다 .
if not,
그렇지 않다면,
Ask them if they have a carriage to go
갈 마차가 있는지 물어보세요
Mengze in Jiangling or Xinze Lake in Guizhao.
Jiangling의 Mengze 또는 Guizhao의 Xinze Lake.
The carriage to Jiangling Mengze must be very big.
Jiangling Mengze로가는 마차는 매우 클 것입니다.
Master Rong is in poor health.
롱 선생님의 건강이 좋지 않습니다.
But if it’s a carriage going to Guizhao Xinze Lake ,
하지만 구이자오 신쩌호로 가는 마차라면 ,
It must be small.
그것은 작아야합니다.
There were too many officers and soldiers along the way.
가는 길에는 장교와 군인이 너무 많았습니다.
If we are recognized on the road
길에서 우리가 인정받는다면
We're done.
이제 끝났습니다.
If none are available, ask them if they have any—
사용할 수 있는 것이 없으면 다음과 같은 것이 있는지 물어보십시오.
stop. Just ask yourself.
멈추다. 스스로에게 물어보세요.
I'll stay and take care of him.
내가 남아서 그를 돌볼게요.
All right.
괜찮은.
Master.
주인.
I'll go find some water.
물 좀 찾으러 갈게요.
We're out of water.
물이 떨어졌어요.
I need to buy some.
좀 사야 해요.
T. Looking for water?
T. 물을 찾고 있나요?
Wait for me here, okay?
여기서 기다려요, 알았죠?
I'll get you a steamed bun to eat.
찐빵 사드릴께요.
steamed stuffed bun?
찐빵?
I'll be back when you finish eating.
식사 끝나면 돌아올게요.
Thanks.
감사해요.
I'll add some seasoning powder for you.
양념가루를 좀 추가해 드릴게요.
Come, get the bread.
자, 빵을 가져오세요.
Take good care of him.
그를 잘 돌봐주세요.
We have the same bread.
우리는 같은 빵을 가지고 있습니다.
Why do you smell so good?
왜 이렇게 좋은 냄새가 나지?
Star Reaching Master,
별 도달 마스터,
It's an honor to spend time with you so close.
이렇게 가까이서 함께 시간을 보낼 수 있어서 영광입니다.
Although the timing is not right,
타이밍이 안맞아도,
I'd like to introduce myself. I am -
나는 내 자신을 소개하고 싶습니다. 그래요 -
You are a pig.
당신은 돼지입니다.
- goodbye. careful. - goodbye.
- 안녕히 가세요. 주의 깊은. - 안녕히 가세요.
(Feiyun Inn) Be careful. Don't slip.
(페이윤 인) 조심하세요. 미끄러지지 마십시오.
gentlemen,
신사,
Is there a carriage to Gangneung and Mengze?
강릉과 맹제까지 가는 마차가 있나요 ?
If not I can rent one.
그렇지 않다면 제가 하나 빌릴 수 있어요.
I'm not sure myself.
나 자신도 잘 모르겠습니다.
Why don't you go in and ask our boss?
들어가서 우리 상사에게 물어보는 게 어때요?
Thanks.
감사해요.
please come in.
오세요.
Is there a carriage from Jiangling to Mengze?
Jiangling에서 Mengze까지 마차가 있습니까?
or Guizhao?
아니면 구이자오?
I'll rent it if you want. I don't mind the cost.
원하시면 빌려드리겠습니다. 나는 비용을 신경 쓰지 않는다.
L-Rongye--
엘-롱예--
Where did you take Yu?
유씨는 어디로 데려갔나요?
???Drink the blues? ? ?
???블루스를 마셔요? ? ?
??? Where love brews into pain? ? ?
??? 사랑이 고통을 불러일으키는 곳은 어디입니까? ? ?
???Can’t wait for the dark night? ? ?
???어두운 밤이 너무 기다려지나요? ? ?
??? Accompanied by flickering candlelight? ? ?
??? 깜박이는 촛불과 함께? ? ?
I won't let you hurt him again
다시는 그 사람을 다치게 놔두지 않을 거야
I will never let you go.
나는 결코 당신을 놓아주지 않을 것입니다.
???I am no longer as impetuous as I was when I was young? ? ?
???나는 이제 어렸을 때처럼 성급하지 않게 됐나요? ? ?
???I heard you were somewhere across the water? ? ?
???물 건너 어딘가에 있다고 들었는데? ? ?
???I want to swim upstream? ? ?
???나는 상류로 수영하고 싶다? ? ?
??? Enjoy the ups and downs of the journey? ? ?
??? 여행의 우여곡절을 즐기시나요? ? ?
??? Lament the waste of life? ? ?
??? 인생의 낭비를 한탄하시나요? ? ?
???Drink the entangled thoughts? ? ?
???얽힌 생각을 마셔? ? ?
???Get drunk, is it so difficult to meet you? ? ?
???취해서 만나기가 그렇게 어렵나요? ? ?
??? Let’s drink to the sadness, shall we? ? ?
??? 슬픔에 술 한잔 하자고 할까? ? ?
??? Gray hair, laughing at me Troubled dreams? ? ?
??? 흰머리, 나를 비웃어요. 꿈이 괴로워요? ? ?
??? After we spent so many days together, I can't forget you? ? ?
??? 우리가 수많은 날을 함께 보낸 뒤에도 나는 당신을 잊을 수 없나요? ? ?
Rong Yu!
유롱!
??? Lament the waste of life? ? ?
??? 인생의 낭비를 한탄하시나요? ? ?
???Drink the entangled thoughts? ? ?
???얽힌 생각을 마셔? ? ?
Let me go!
날 보내줘!
??? Gray hair, laughing at me Troubled dreams? ? ?
??? 흰머리, 나를 비웃어요. 꿈이 괴로워요? ? ?
??? After we spent so many days together, I can't forget you? ? ?
??? 우리가 수많은 날을 함께 보낸 뒤에도 나는 당신을 잊을 수 없나요? ? ?
??? Enjoy the ups and downs of the journey? ? ?
??? 여행의 우여곡절을 즐기시나요? ? ?
Rong Yu!
유롱!
???Drink the entangled thoughts? ? ?
???얽힌 생각을 마셔? ? ?
???Get drunk, is it so difficult to meet you? ? ?
???취해서 만나기가 그렇게 어렵나요? ? ?
??? Let’s drink to the sadness, shall we? ? ?
??? 슬픔에 술 한잔 하자고 할까? ? ?
??? Gray hair, laughing at me Troubled dreams? ? ?
??? 흰머리, 나를 비웃어요. 꿈이 괴로워요? ? ?
??? After we spent so many days together, I can't forget you? ? ?
??? 우리가 수많은 날을 함께 보낸 뒤에도 나는 당신을 잊을 수 없나요? ? ?
Jiuling.
지울링.
Thank you for sending my daughter home.
내 딸을 집으로 보내주셔서 감사합니다.
- Tell Master Rong that I can't see him today. - Are you hurt? How are you?
- 롱 선생님께 오늘은 만날 수 없다고 전해주세요. - 다쳤어요? 어떻게 지내세요?
I will apologize to him personally tomorrow.
내일 그 사람에게 직접 사과하겠습니다.
General He,
그 장군님,
My master said it was not necessary.
주인님은 그럴 필요 없다고 하더군요.
He also said that people from the He family should not come to Rongfu again.
그는 또한 He 가족이 다시는 Rongfu에 와서는 안된다고 말했습니다.
What?
무엇?
You're not injured, are you? your hands? ? ?
당신은 부상을 입지 않았죠? 네 손은? ? ?
Why are your hands tied?
손은 왜 묶인 걸까요?
Zong Ming, call the doctor.
종밍 씨, 의사를 불러주세요.
The Rong family does not want Rong Yu to go to Mount Wuhua.
Rong 가족은 Rong Yu가 Wuhua 산에가는 것을 원하지 않습니다 .
No matter what, you insist on taking him away.
무슨 일이 있어도 당신은 그를 데려가겠다고 고집합니다.
I don't care about Rong Yu.
나는 Rong Yu에 관심이 없습니다.
but if something happens to you
하지만 너에게 무슨 일이 생기면
How will my father and I get through this?
아버지와 나는 이 상황을 어떻게 극복할 수 있을까요?
enough. Fortunately she's back.
충분한. 다행히 그녀는 돌아왔습니다.
I must say.
꼭 말해야겠습니다.
Didn't you hear what that man just said?
그 사람이 방금 한 말 못 들었어?
He said: "People from the He family should not go to Rong Mansion again."
그는 "허씨 가문 사람들은 다시는 롱맨션에 가서는 안 된다"고 말했다.
Let’s see what Jiang Rong did.
Jiang Rong이 무엇을했는지 봅시다.
Rong Yu was still unconscious, so he gave us an engagement gift.
용우는 아직 의식이 없어서 우리에게 약혼 선물을 주었습니다.
Is he still human?
그는 아직도 인간인가요?
Is the Rong family worth your risk?
Rong 가족이 위험을 감수할 가치가 있나요?
Qiuting.
큐팅.
Father.
아버지.
In fact, Rong Yu was already awake.
사실 유용준은 이미 깨어난 상태였다.
Really?
정말?
That's good news.
좋은 소식이군요.
Jiuling,
지울링,
Although you are a bit reckless,
조금 무모하긴 하지만,
You end up with a good result.
마무리하시면 좋은 결과 있으실 겁니다.
You should be happy about this.
당신은 이것에 대해 행복해야합니다.
I want to live a happy life.
나는 행복한 삶을 살고 싶다.
But I am not happy at all.
그러나 나는 전혀 행복하지 않습니다.
- Jiuling. - Jiuling!
- 지울링 - 지울링!
Jiuling!
지울링!
Master, Master, you can't go out.
스승님, 스승님, 나가시면 안 됩니다.
Master, you can't go out.
선생님, 나가시면 안 돼요.
Master.
주인.
You can't go out.
당신은 나갈 수 없습니다.
Yong adult,
용인,
I am ashamed.
나는 부끄러워.
The young master’s current situation
젊은 스승의 현재 상황
This is something I rarely see in my life.
이것은 내 인생에서 거의 볼 수 없는 것입니다.
So I can only try to prescribe a few medicines,
그래서 몇 가지 약만 처방하려고 노력할 수 있는데,
Hopefully they can make him better.
그들이 그를 더 좋게 만들 수 있기를 바랍니다.
So is he this kind of person?
그럼 그 사람이 이런 사람인가?
Stupid?
멍청한?
He doesn't remember anything.
그는 아무것도 기억하지 못합니다.
But why does he only remember her?
그런데 왜 그는 그녀만 기억하는 걸까?
Why does he want her?
그 사람은 왜 그녀를 원하는 걸까요?
Why must it be her?
왜 그녀여야만 하는가?
Lord Rong, this is not difficult to understand.
롱 경, 이것은 이해하기 어렵지 않습니다.
Newborn ducks and goslings
갓 태어난 오리와 새끼 기러기
Will stick to the first person
첫 번째 사람에게 충실합니다
They watch.
그들은 지켜본다.
The young master’s current mental state
젊은 스승의 현재 정신상태
Just like a newborn baby.
갓 태어난 아기처럼.
When he was conscious, Miss He was the only one around him.
그가 의식이 있었을 때 그의 주변에는 Miss He만이 있었습니다.
He naturally thinks that she is the closest person to him
그는 자연스럽게 그녀가 자신과 가장 가까운 사람이라고 생각합니다
Feeling uneasy if she wasn't there.
그 사람이 없으면 불안할 것 같아요.
The people closest to you? ? ?
가장 가까운 사람들? ? ?
This will make the Rong family fall out.
이로 인해 Rong 가족이 무너질 것입니다.
upside down.
상하 반전.
Master, Master, you can't go out.
스승님, 스승님, 나가시면 안 됩니다.
Yes.
예.
Master, you can't go out.
선생님, 나가시면 안 돼요.
I'll go back to the Imperial Medical Bureau to discuss it with everyone.
나는 제국 의료국으로 돌아가서 모두와 논의하겠습니다.
I'll take my leave first.
먼저 휴가를 가겠습니다.
Master, you can't go out.
선생님, 나가시면 안 돼요.
Master, please stop.
선생님, 그만하세요.
Master? ? ?
주인? ? ?
The young master woke up.
젊은 주인이 일어났습니다.
Heshan, did you hear that?
허샨, 들었어?
future,
미래에
You are still his bodyguard.
당신은 여전히 ​​그의 경호원입니다.
thank you for your kindness.
당신의 친절에 감사드립니다.
But I can't forgive your betrayal
하지만 난 너의 배신을 용서할 수 없어
A member of the Rong family.
롱 가문의 일원.
crime
범죄
It's my responsibility alone.
그건 나 혼자만의 책임이다.
Leave a decent person behind
괜찮은 사람을 남겨두고
By the young master's side.
젊은 주인 옆에서.
Master, I have something to ask you.
선생님, 부탁드릴 게 있어요.
Yu, here.
유, 여기요.
Let's eat.
먹자.
Take these.
이것을 가져가세요.
OK Catch them.
좋아요 그들을 잡아.
Yu, this soup is your favorite.
유, 이 수프가 당신이 가장 좋아하는 것 같아요.
here.
여기.
Come.
오다.
Have some soup.
수프를 드세요.
Do you want to eat steamed buns?
찐빵 먹을래?
here.
여기.
Come one
하나 오세요
Eat it.
그것을 먹을.
Doesn't it taste good?
맛이 좋지 않나요?
Someone!
누구!
gentlemen.
신사.
Tell the kitchen to make bread when possible.
가능하면 부엌에 빵을 만들어 달라고 말하세요 .
return,
반품,
Go outside and buy a variety of bread in the city.
밖에 나가서 시내에서 다양한 빵을 사보세요.
go.
가다.
Sir, the bakery only does business in the early morning.
선생님, 그 빵집은 이른 아침에만 영업을 합니다.
Then bring those bakers back to make bread here.
그런 다음 빵 굽는 사람을 다시 불러와서 여기에서 빵을 만들어 보세요.
Give them double wages.
그들에게 두 배의 임금을 주십시오.
Do you need me to teach you?
내가 가르쳐야 합니까?
I'm on my way now.
지금 가는 중이에요.
At.
에.
Master!
주인!
sorry.
죄송합니다.
you're awake. That's great.
당신은 깨어있습니다. 훌륭해요.
Rong Yu!
유롱!
Jiuling!
지울링!
your hands!
당신의 손!
Your left hand is just your support hand.
당신의 왼손은 단지 당신의 지지 손일 뿐입니다.
Don't rush to exercise it yet.
아직 서두르지 마십시오.
Martial arts practitioners should not rush for success.
무술 수련자는 성공을 위해 서두르면 안 됩니다.
I don't.
나는 아니에요.
Don't you want to become stronger?
강해지고 싶지 않아?
But now you're too eager.
하지만 지금 당신은 너무 열심이에요.
Even if you can use a sword now,
지금은 검을 쓸 수 있다고 해도
I can beat you with my bare feet.
나는 맨발로 당신을 이길 수 있습니다.
What's wrong with wanting to become stronger?
강해지고 싶은 게 뭐가 문제야?
future,
미래에
No one can hurt anyone in front of me.
내 앞에 있는 사람은 누구도 해칠 수 없습니다.
No one can take anyone away from me.
누구도 나에게서 누군가를 빼앗을 수 없습니다.
I know.
알아요.
you do not know.
넌 몰라.
Ten years in Wuhua Mountain,
오화산에서 10년,
My master and senior brother protected me.
나의 주인님과 형님이 나를 보호해 주셨습니다.
You will protect me when I come back.
내가 돌아올 때 당신은 나를 보호해 주실 것입니다.
But I can't protect anyone.
하지만 나는 누구도 보호할 수 없어요.
Didn't you say before that you are the best in the world?
전에 당신이 세계 최고 라고 말하지 않았나요 ?
That's just nonsense.
그건 말도 안되는 소리입니다.
Don't use it against me.
나에게 불리하게 사용하지 마십시오.
Meet me at the training ground
훈련장에서 만나요
Tomorrow morning, let's go exercise.
내일 아침에는 운동하러 가자.
Can you get up on time?
제시간에 일어날 수 있나요?
I can.
저 할 수 있어요.
If you really want to learn martial arts
정말 무술을 배우고 싶다면
We won't pamper you like we would at home.
우리는 집에서처럼 당신을 애지중지하지 않을 것입니다.
I don't need to indulge.
나는 탐닉할 필요가 없습니다.
(To disciple Jiuling)
(구릉(九陵) 제자에게)
I have a deep hatred for Xingxiang Pavilion.
나는 Xingxiang Pavilion에 대해 깊은 증오심을 가지고 있습니다.
Therefore, the life and death of the people in that place have nothing to do with me.
그러므로 그 곳 사람들의 삶과 죽음은 나와는 아무 상관이 없습니다.
I will soon leave the mountains and travel.
나는 곧 산을 떠나 여행을 떠날 것이다.
Don't come to me.
나에게 오지 마세요.
What kind of ancient history does it have?
어떤 종류의 고대 역사가 있습니까?
Can my master be allowed to harbor such hatred?
나의 주인이 그런 증오를 품도록 허락될 수 있습니까?
It must be painful.
고통스러울 것 같아요.
Must I make my master give up her hatred?
주인님이 증오심을 버리게 해야 할까요?
For the mistakes I made?
내가 저지른 실수 때문에?
Senior brother, there is something wrong with amnesia.
선배님, 기억상실증이 뭔가 문제가 있는 것 같아요.
After taking it,
복용 후,
Not only did Rong Yu not sever emotional ties,
Rong Yu는 감정적 유대를 끊지 않았을뿐만 아니라
But it also hurt mentally.
하지만 정신적으로도 상처를 입었습니다.
I need a prescription for an antidote.
해독제 처방이 필요해요.
I hope to get a reply soon.
곧 답변을 받을 수 있기를 바랍니다.
Free blood vine grass and dragon head ginseng
블러드덩굴풀 과 용머리삼 무료 제공
I quickly found Jia Lin.
나는 Jia Lin을 빨리 찾았습니다.
Your Highness,
전하,
These are healing treasures
치유의 보물이군요
You have found it for our king.
당신은 우리 왕을 위해 그것을 찾았습니다.
It took you two years
2년이 걸렸어요
Finally got a foothold.
드디어 발판을 마련했습니다.
Now, we are at the point where the king is re-electing his successor.
이제 우리는 왕이 후계자를 다시 선출하는 시점에 와 있습니다.
So please don't do this.
그러니 제발 이러지 마세요.
Hurry to Jialin. This matter need not be discussed any further.
서둘러 지알린으로 가세요. 이 문제는 더 이상 논의할 필요가 없습니다.
please come in.
오세요.
OK
좋아요
this way please.
이쪽으로 오십시오.
How is it going?
어떻게 지내요?
Healing treasure.
힐링의 보물.
careful.
주의 깊은.
hurry up!
서둘러요!
Hold steady. And thrust!
가만히 있어라. 그리고 밀어붙여라!
Miss, are you also here to see the young master?
아가씨, 당신도 젊은 스승님을 만나러 오셨나요?
I'm afraid you're here in vain.
당신이 여기까지 온 것이 헛된 일인가 두렵습니다.
Something happened to the young master recently.
최근 젊은 스승에게 무슨 일이 일어났습니다.
He hasn't been out for a while.
그는 한동안 밖에 나오지 않았습니다.
There used to be a lot of people waiting here
예전엔 여기서 기다리는 사람이 많았는데
Just to take a look at him.
그를 한번 살펴보려고요.
But things have changed.
그러나 상황이 바뀌었습니다.
Even my tea stall business has declined.
찻집 사업도 쇠퇴했어요.
Can you make me a pot of tea?
차 한 주전자 만들어 주실 수 있나요?
OK
좋아요
I also heard
나도 들었어
He seemed to have become a fool.
그는 바보가 된 것 같았다.
He couldn't eat or speak.
그는 먹을 수도, 말할 수도 없었습니다.
However, you still like him.
그러나 당신은 여전히 ​​​​그를 좋아합니다.
You're the only person I've seen in a while.
당신은 내가 한동안 본 유일한 사람입니다.
He is not a fool.
그는 바보가 아닙니다.
Well, he's not.
글쎄, 그는 그렇지 않습니다.
Fool.
바보.
What an idiot.
이런 멍청이 같으니라고.
The last time my father and I were here, he was just staring at a bun.
저번에 아버지와 제가 여기 왔을 때 아버지는 빵을 바라보고 계셨어요.
This time we came and he was still staring at the pancakes.
이번에 우리가 왔는데 그는 여전히 팬케이크를 쳐다보고 있었습니다.
Don't you think he looks like the same person?
그 사람이랑 똑같은 사람인 것 같지 않아?
He looks just like the dog you fed bread to last time.
지난번에 빵을 먹였던 개와 꼭 닮았네요.
Exactly.
정확히.
You also noticed his gaze, right?
그의 시선도 눈치채셨죠?
Yes, the eyes are exactly the same.
네, 눈은 똑같습니다.
I was going to throw a stone at him
그 사람한테 돌을 던질 뻔 했어요
While the two guards were not paying attention.
두 명의 경비원은주의를 기울이지 않았습니다.
I want to see if he really can't speak
그 사람이 정말 말을 못하는지 확인하고 싶어요.
Or dodge.
아니면 피하세요.
Who hit me?
누가 나를 때렸나요?
Your nose is bleeding. How are you?
코피가 나네요. 어떻게 지내세요?
- Sir, do you need me to wipe the blood for you? - Who hit me?
- 선생님, 제가 피를 닦아 드릴까요? - 누가 나를 때렸나요?
Who wants your damn rag?
누가 네 망할 걸레를 갖고 싶어?
- How are you? - who is it?
- 어떻게 지내세요? - 누구예요?
is her.
그녀야.
go.
가다.
you? ? ?
너? ? ?
H-He Jiuling.
H-He Jiuling.
Did you throw a stone?
돌을 던졌나요?
Tell me, did you throw a stone?
말해봐, 돌을 던졌어?
NO, I have not. The guards in the mansion were watching closely.
아니요, 그렇지 않습니다. 저택의 경비병들이 유심히 지켜보고 있었다.
This is just my idea.
이것은 단지 내 생각이다.
I didn't really throw it.
진짜 안 던졌는데
Ouch, it hurts. Miss He! Miss He!
아야, 아파. 미스 그! 미스 그!
Give me a steamed bun.
찐빵 주세요.
OK
좋아요
Miss He, what do you want to do?
Miss He님은 무엇을 하고 싶으신가요?
Here, miss.
여기요, 아가씨.
This is the bun I gave you. Eat it.
이건 내가 준 빵이야. 그것을 먹을.
Eat it with gratitude.
감사한 마음으로 드세요.
Eat it.
그것을 먹을.
Eat it now.
지금 먹어라.
eat.
먹다.
He Jiuling, we want to stand up for you.
He Jiuling, 우리는 당신을 옹호하고 싶습니다.
Your Majesty has granted him your marriage.
폐하께서 그에게 결혼을 허락하셨습니다.
But now he has become a fool.
그러나 이제 그는 바보가 되었습니다.
How does he deserve you?
그 사람은 당신에게 어떤 자격이 있습니까?
What does it have to do with you?
그게 당신과 무슨 관련이 있나요?
if you keep talking nonsense
계속 헛소리하면
Next time I will give you more than just a piece of bread.
다음에는 빵 한 조각보다 더 많은 것을 주겠습니다.
YY-you? ? ? You are lawless.
당신은요? ? ? 당신은 불법입니다.
Have you forgotten the fate of the young master?
젊은 스승의 운명을 잊으셨나요?
- Sir, should we stop this? - Everyone, get out!
- 선생님, 이걸 멈춰야 할까요? - 다들 나가!
They came here under the pretext of visiting the sick to see the spectacle.
그들은 광경을 보기 위해 병자들을 방문한다는 구실로 이곳에 왔습니다.
I can't teach them a lesson.
나는 그들에게 교훈을 줄 수 없습니다.
Let her hit them.
그녀가 그들을 때리게 놔두세요.
gentlemen,
신사,
The young master is not in good health.
젊은 주인은 건강이 좋지 않습니다.
The buns are broken.
빵이 부러졌습니다.
Buy more.
더 사.
Yes.
예.
Miss He.
미스 헤.
Did Rong Yu???
유롱이 그랬나요???
your face? ? ?
너의 얼굴? ? ?
nothing.
아무것도 아님.
How could there be nothing?
어떻게 아무것도 없을 수 있니?
Is it all because of me? ? ?
다 나 때문인가? ? ?
I need to go back.
나는 돌아가야 한다.
The young master is not in a good mood.
젊은 주인은 기분이 좋지 않습니다.
He hardly slept or ate.
그는 잠도 거의 자지 않았고 식사도 하지 않았습니다.
All he does is stare at the bun all day long.
그가 하는 일은 하루 종일 빵을 쳐다보는 것 뿐이다.
I'll add some seasoning powder for you.
양념가루를 좀 추가해 드릴게요.
I'll be back when you finish eating.
식사 끝나면 돌아올게요.
I think I know why he stopped eating.
그 사람이 왜 식사를 중단했는지 알 것 같아요.
I'll go and buy.
내가 가서 사올게.
Miss He.
미스 헤.
Can I go visit the young master?
젊은 스승님을 만나러 갈 수 있나요?
No, I won't go.
아니요, 안 갈 거예요.
I can't bring anyone else down.
나는 다른 사람을 실망시킬 수 없습니다.
Don't worry.
괜찮아요.
No one will be punished again.
다시는 누구도 처벌받지 않을 것입니다.
Master.
주인.
Master, go this way.
선생님, 이쪽으로 가세요.
Master, please slow down.
선생님, 천천히 해주세요.
slowly.
느리게.
Come.
오다.
Take your time, Master.
천천히 하세요, 마스터.
Master, look!
선생님, 보세요!
???Under the sunset at dusk? ? ?
???해질녘 노을 아래서요? ? ?
???I traveled thousands of miles to a distant place? ? ?
???나는 먼 곳으로 수천 마일을 여행했다고요? ? ?
???Playing the piano under the moonlight? ? ?
???달빛아래 피아노 연주? ? ?
???These drinks won’t make me forget? ? ?
???이 음료수는 잊혀지지 않을까요? ? ?
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
???내가 당신을 위해 쓴 소망은요? ? ?
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있다고? ? ?
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 최강의 와인을 좋아하시나요? ? ?
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 운명을 피할 방법은 없나요? ? ?
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
???뒤돌아보니 기다리고 있는거 보이시죠? ? ?
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
???우리의 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔으로 가득 차 있습니까? ? ?
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 밝은 은하계로 결정화되기를 원하시나요 ???
???You quietly turned around and closed the marriage certificate? ? ?
??? 조용히 돌아서서 결혼증명서를 닫았나요? ? ?
???Ask how many stars are there in the sky? ? ?
???하늘에 별이 몇 개 있는지 물어보세요. ? ?
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
???내가 당신을 위해 쓴 소망은요? ? ?
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있다고? ? ?
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 최강의 와인을 좋아하시나요? ? ?
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 운명을 피할 방법은 없나요? ? ?
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
???뒤돌아보니 기다리고 있는거 보이시죠? ? ?
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
???우리의 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔으로 가득 차 있습니까? ? ?
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 밝은 은하계로 결정화되기를 원하시나요 ???
???I gently caress the guzheng, waiting for passers-by like you???
???나는 고젱을 부드럽게 어루만지며 당신같은 행인을 기다린다???
???So you are my indissoluble bond? ? ?
???그럼 당신은 나의 불용성 유대인가요? ? ?
???Under the sunset at dusk? ? ?
???해질녘 노을 아래서요? ? ?
???I traveled thousands of miles to a distant place? ? ?
???나는 먼 곳으로 수천 마일을 여행했다고요? ? ?
???Playing the piano under the moonlight? ? ?
???달빛아래 피아노 연주? ? ?
???These drinks won’t make me forget? ? ?
???이 음료수는 잊혀지지 않을까요? ? ?
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
???내가 당신을 위해 쓴 소망은요? ? ?
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있다고? ? ?
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 최강의 와인을 좋아하시나요? ? ?
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 운명을 피할 방법은 없나요? ? ?
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
???뒤돌아보니 기다리고 있는거 보이시죠? ? ?
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
???우리의 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔으로 가득 차 있습니까? ? ?
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 밝은 은하계로 결정화되기를 원하시나요 ???
???You quietly turned around and closed the marriage certificate? ? ?
??? 조용히 돌아서서 결혼증명서를 닫았나요? ? ?
???Ask how many stars are there in the sky? ? ?
???하늘에 별이 몇 개 있는지 물어보세요. ? ?
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
???내가 당신을 위해 쓴 소망은요? ? ?
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있다고? ? ?
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 최강의 와인을 좋아하시나요? ? ?
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 운명을 피할 방법은 없나요? ? ?
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
???뒤돌아보니 기다리고 있는거 보이시죠? ? ?
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
???우리의 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔으로 가득 차 있습니까? ? ?
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 밝은 은하계로 결정화되기를 원하시나요 ???
???I gently caress the guzheng, waiting for passers-by like you???
???나는 고젱을 부드럽게 어루만지며 당신같은 행인을 기다린다???
???So you are my indissoluble bond? ? ?
???그럼 당신은 나의 불용성 유대인가요? ? ?